Daniel Jin

Full-Stack Software Engineer, Blockchain Developer ittechhunter513@gmail.com

Summary

Dedicated developer with over 9 years of experience in the full-stack software engineering including blockchain industries. Passionate about self-learning new technologies and building new products. Ability to translate business requirements into technical solutions. Well versed in major programming languages, frameworks and dev environment. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong Communication
- Complex problem solver

Programming Languages:

PHP, Ruby, Java, Python, HTML, Javascript, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Node.js

Blockchain Skills:

Solidity, Rust, FunC, Ethereum, BSC, Solana, NEAR, TON, DeFi, DAO, NFT, DApp

- Quick-Delivery of Work
- Service-focused
- Full-time & Hardworking

Frameworks and Libraries:

Laravel, Ruby on Rails, Spring Boot, React/Next.js, Vue.js/Nuxt.js, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

Other Skills:

SOAP, Robot framework , Openshift Kubernetes, Kocker , Agile team , SCRUM, OO programming

Experience

Full Stack Developer, Cyber Web

6/2022 to Present

- Developed DAO project based on TON and BSC (https://www.figma.com/file/sJmx0vER2bBd04n3jrKcZh/DAO-Dream-%2F-Landing-Page)
- Developed a sports betting app based on TON (https://ozare-e8ed6.firebaseapp.com)
- Developed a staking service based on NEAR
 (https://drive.google.com/file/d/1WXPTXFFklc6rI7Bv5Qd-aHMrTgWUCgFg/view?usp=drive_link)

1/2022 to 8/2022

- Built front-end of a staking service (http://app.invisicash.org)
- Built front-end of Streeth NFT market place (https://www.streeth.app)
- Built front-end of Moosma NFT market place (https://marketplace.moonsama.com/collections)
- Built front-end of Helix App (https://helixapp.com/)

Smart Contract Developer, Dystopia Labs

1/2022 to 3/2022

- Developed an airdrop claimable smart contract
- Made a web3 event ticketing platform

Blockchain Developer, SushiSwap

5/2021 to 3/2022

- Made an IDO (auction platform) MISO (https://miso.sushi.com)
- Upgraded SushiSwap interface to v2 (https://app.sushi.com)
- Made a subgraph for BentoBox

Blockchain Developer, CandySwap

1/2021 to 2/2021

- Forked and updated PancakeSwap interface for CandySwap
- Forked and updated PancakeSwap contracts for CandySwap

Blockchain Developer, Tokenizer

5/2020 to 9/2020

- Created a new token TMP forked from ERC-20
- Implemented DAO for exchange

Blockchain Developer, AnjiEco

6/2019 to 7/2021

- Built a DEX website (https://app.anji.eco)
- Developed a staking contract for AnjiEco

Full Stack Developer, Sequoia Software

12/2014 to 3/2019

- Collaborated with teams to define software requirements and create technical designs
- Built the front-end and back-end of web applications using modern web development technologies
- Wrote clean, maintainable, and testable code that adheres to industry best practices
- Developed and maintained databases and integrating them with web applications
- Troubleshooted and debugged code to identify and fix errors
- Continuously learned and stayed up-to-date with new technologies, tools, and best practices in software development

Education

Bachelor's Degree Computer Science Faculty of Engineering, Architecture and Information Technology

University of Queensland

September 2014 ~ April 2018

St Lucia, Australia